Guide to the Public Administration Reports and Studies (Assorted), 1910-1992 AIS.1996.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Reports on Pittsburgh (city), 1910-1985; IV.
  - Department of City Planning, 1913-1980; 1.
    - School Study for the Are North of the Rivers, Preliminary Staff Report, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - School Study for the Are South of the Rivers, A City Rebuilds, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sheraden Housing Redevelopment Area Plan, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Six-year Development 1975-1980, Progress Report (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Smith (Wilbur) & Associates Strip District short-renege traffic improvements study, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Southside Park, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Street Improvement Program, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - The Multi-Problem Family and Urban Renewal, Community Renewal Program, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Citizen Committee on City Plan, 1921-1923; 2.
    - A Major Street Plan for Pittsburgh, Report No.2, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Parks: a part of the Pittsburgh Plan, Report No. 4, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Transit: a part of the Pittsburgh Plan, Report No. 3, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Waterways: a part of the Pittsburgh Plan, Report No. 6, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Graduate School of Public and International Affairs, 1963-1979; 3.
    - Allegheny West Final Project Report Part I- Application for Loan and Grant, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Application for Loan and Grant Part 1, Hamilton-Larimer, Slum Clearance and Urban Renewal Program, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Application for Loan and Grant Part I, Final Project Report, Larimer Avenue, Urban Renewal Conservation Project, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - An Analysis of the Evaluation of ESEA Title I Programs-Pittsburgh Public Schools (Thesis) by Stromberg, Arlene M., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Building Better Cities: Human Values in Renewal, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Community Action Pittsburgh: Selected Aspects of Citizen Participation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Industrial Development Policies and Programs for Community Development and Action, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Land Use Plan for the South Side Flats, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Market Square Study, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - NASPAA Self-Study Report Volume I, Sections I-X, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - NASPAA Self-Study Report Volume II, Faculty Date Sheets and Course Abstracts, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - The Pittsburgh Renaissance Project: the Stanton Belfour Oral History Collection; Final Report, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Urban Renewal Workshop IV Hamilton Larimer Group B (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - What to expect, Home Builders Association of Metropolitan Pittsburgh, Community Growth Conference (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Office of Planning and Budget, 1975-1977; 4.
    - Planning and Resource Management, Data Collection Manual, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Response of The University of Pittsburgh to The Joint State Government Commission Analysis of Faculty Output and Salary Costs of State-Related Universities (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1963-1979; 5.
    - Industrial Databook for the Pittsburgh district. Bureau of Business Research Statistical Handbooks, Number 2, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Perspectives on Motivations of Volunteers: Pittsburgh SMSA, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Physical aspects of neighborhood preservation: considerations of citizen participation, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Planning for Future Capital Requirements, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings, Sanitary Engineering Conference, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Public Health Laws of The City of Pittsburgh, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - A Study of the Governance of the University of Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - The pattern of borough government, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - The Planning of Tax Acquired Property for public use in The City of Pittsburgh, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Transportation and Economic Study relating to Water Transportation of Coal, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Transportation and Economic Study relating to Water Transportation of Coal, Executive Summary, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Office of Secretary/Office of Vice Chancellor for Program Development and Public Affairs (University of Urban Interface Program), 1969-1972; 6.
    - University-Urban Interface Program: Proposal for continuation of a University-Urban Interface Program, ("University-Urban Interface Program: Proposal for continuation of a University-Urban Interface Program," online pending), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: Phase II Interim Report (April - June, 1970), ("University-Urban Interface Program: Phase II Interim Report (April - June, 1970)," online pending), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 1 (July - September, 1971), ("University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 1 (July - September, 1971)," online pending) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 2 (October - December, 1971), ("University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 2 (October - December, 1971)," online pending) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 3 (January - March, 1972), ("University-Urban Interface Program: Phase III Progress Report 3 (January - March, 1972)," online pending) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: The Student Consultant Project (SCP): A Case Study of Student Involvement in social action, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - University-Urban Interface Program: A University And Its Community Confront Problems and Goals, ("University-Urban Interface Program: A University And Its Community Confront Problems and Goals," online pending), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Pittsburgh Regional Plan Association, 1911-1970; 7.
    - Annual Report, 1953-61 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Borough of Sharpsburg Long Range Development Plan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Building Code of the City of Pittsburgh, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Main Thoroughfares and the Down Town District, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - A Model of Metropolis, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Oakland and the Golden Triangle, a Conceptual Critique, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Prelude to the Future, Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Report on Proposed New Stadium, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Route Eight Study: A Proposal for Highway Renewal (Oversize), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, 1952-1969; 8.
    - Allegheny Center, from a rich history, a new way of life, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Allegheny General Hospital Redevelopment Area - Proposed, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Final Project Report: Larimer Avenue Renewal Project, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Fiscal Planning for An Urban Community, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Land Disposition Documents for Chateau Street West Redevelopment Area No. 11, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Land Disposition Documents for East Liberty Redevelopment Area No. 10, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Links to Better Urban Living: Application to the Department of Housing and Urban Development for a Grant to plan a comprehensive city demonstration program, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Lower Hill Redevelopment Project, Land Disposition Documents, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Part I- Application for Loan and Grant, Homewood North Conservation Project, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Part I- Application for Loan and Grant, Larimer Avenue Conservation Project, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Part I- Application for Loan and Grant, Woods Run Urban Renewal Project, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Part II- Application for Loan and Grant, Woods Run Urban Renewal Project, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Progress Report, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Proposal for the Redevelopment of Redevelopment Area No. 12 in the 22nd Ward of the City of Pittsburgh, County of Allegheny, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Proposal for the Redevelopment of a Part of Redevelopment Area No. 15, Urban Renewal Project, Woods Run., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Proposal for the Redevelopment of Redevelopment Area No. 4 and Partial Redevelopment of Redevelopment Area No. 5, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Proposal for the Redevelopment of Redevelopment Area No. 10, East Liberty, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Proposal for the Redevelopment of A Part of Redevelopment Area No. 11, Chateau Street West, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Report of Progress, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Review of Progress Under the Program for Community Improvements for the Elimination and Prevention of Slums and Blight in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Status Report, Pittsburgh Urban Renewal Program, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Status Report: Project Area Report, Pittsburgh Urban Renewal Program, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Changing City, Report of the Urban Redevelopment Authoity of Pittsburgh, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Urban Renewal Plan: Bluff Street Urban Renewal Project; Redevelopment Area No. 6, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Urban Renewal Plan: Chateau Street West, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Various, 1941-1982; 9.
    - Bikeways for Pittsburgh, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Current Variables affecting the urban orchestra: the case of the Pittsburgh Symphony by Schlesinger, Janet, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Planning for Pittsburgh's Hill District, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Historic and June 1972 Flood Elevations; Greater Pittsburgh Region; Land and Water Studies for Environmental Analysis (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Golden Triangle Employment, East Rapid Line Planning Studies, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Golden Triangle School Population, East Rapid Line Planning Studies, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Hours and Earnings in Manufacturing and Selected Nonmanufacturing Industries: Pittsburgh Labor Market Area, 1960-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - How to save and create Jobs in the Pittsburgh Area, An Analysis of Chronic Unemployment by Harold J. Ruttenberg, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Market Square Study by Altayli, E., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Part One of the Report of the Point Park Commission, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Area Transportation Study, 1980 Network Study Procedures for Determining Arterial Improvements and Costs by Witheford, David, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Hospital Manual, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Lutheran Planning Study, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh's Traffic Problem: An Immediate Solution with Rail Transit by Vranich, Joseph, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Priority Program, Freeways in City of Pittsburgh, 1964-1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Profile of Poverty in Pittsburgh, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Progress Report, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Progress Report by Douglas, Neiland J., Jr., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Proposed draft enabling ordinance for the granting of a cable television franchise for the ciy of Pittsburgh, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Public Hearing Conducted by Governor's Committee on Urban Mass Transportation, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Public Parking Authority Operation in Chicago, Pittsburgh and Detroit; A panel Discussion, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Regulating cable communications in the city of Pittsburgh: agreement, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Regulating cable communications in the city of Pittsburgh, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Report on Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Seminar, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Report on Renewal by Pease, Robert B., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Report on the City of Pittsburgh, Penna., Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Residential Solid Waste Systems for the Pittsburgh Region: Analyses of Five Alternatives, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Results of a Technological Review of the Proposed Transit Expressway Revenue Line (TERL) in Pittsburgh, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Smoke Controller in Pittsburgh and Allengheny County, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Special Funding Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - A Study of Some Aspects of Leisure Time Services, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - A Summarization of the Opinions and Recommendations of the Principal Older Studies of Mass Transportation in the Pittsburgh Area, c. 1950 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - The First ten years, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Planning of Tax Acquired Property for Public Use in the City of Pittsburgh by Lowry, Ralph L., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - The Public Schools and the Public, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - The Story of Pittsburgh's No. 1 Headache, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Transportation Requirements and Effects of New Communities- Study in New Systems of Urban Transportation, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Urban Renewal. A Series of Articles by Mel Seidenberg, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - A Neighborhood Program for Youth-By Youth, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Veterans Administration Hospitals, "The Renaissance City", Undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Department of City Controller, 1977-1978; 10.
    - Performance Audit of the Animal Control Program, City of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Performance Audit of the Department of City Treasurer, Water Assessors Section, City of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Performance Audit of the Department of Environmental Service, City of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Performance Audit of the Department of Supplies, Bureau of Automotive Equipment, City of Pittsburgh, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Performance Audit of the Department of Water, City of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Department of Water, 1959-1960; 11.
    - City of Pittsburgh Water Works, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - City of Pittsburgh Water Works, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Greater Pittsburgh (International) Airport, 1968-1972; 12.
    - Master Plan and Land Use Report, Greater Pittsburgh Airport, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Operational Manual, Volume I, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Operational Manual, Volume II, Emergency Plan, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Stadium Authority of Pittsburgh, 1964-1985; 13.
    - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Future Development Prospectus: Pittsburgh Stadium Project (Oversize), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Report on Examination of Financial Statements and Additional Information, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - The Stadium- A Focal Point of the Renaissance: Official Program Presentation, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Urban Renewal Project Information, c.1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1965-1978; 14.
    - Manpower Resource and Retrieval Service: A Computerized Approach, Volume I, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Manpower Resource and Retrieval Service: A Computerized Approach, Volume II, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Statement on Educational Needs in the Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - The Pittsburgh Free Clinic Inc., 1976-1981; 15.
    - Annual Report, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 11th Annual Report, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - An Assessment of the Current Patient Population of the Family Planning, Day Medical and Evening Walk-In Programs by Windell, Phillip A., 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Action-Housing Inc. (Allegheny Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods), 1959-1977; 16.
    - Application for a grant from the Ford Foundation for a test demonstration of urban extension, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - An Evaluation of Pittsburgh's Neighborhood Housing Services Program, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - General Information, East Liberty Urban Renewal, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Midway Report, Action for Employment, A demonstration Neighborhood Manpower Project, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Nineteeth Annual Survey of New Housing Construction for Sale and Rent in the Pittsburgh Area, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Plan of Operations for Urban Extension, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Plan of Operations, Neighborhood Urban Extension, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - A Proposal, Pittsburgh Development Fund, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Proposals for Participation in the Community Action Program of the City of Pittsburgh to be Carried Out Under Title II of the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Summary Proceedings of Clinic on Residential Rehabilitation Under Sections 220 and 221 of the National Housing Act, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Summary Proceedings of Second Annual Neighborhood Development Workshop for Neighborhood Leaders, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Twelfth Annual Survey of New Housing Construction for Sale and Rent in the Pittsburgh Area, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Urban Extension. Proceedings of the Pittsburgh Urban Extension Conference and Application For a Grant From The Ford Foundation for a Test Demonstration, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Human Relations, 1959-1977; 17.
    - Racial practices in Pittsburgh hospitals, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - The Status of Education of Negroes in Pittsburgh by Aurbach, Herbert A., 1960 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Studies of School Desegregation and Achievement, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - The Mayor's Commission on Human Relations, 1964-1966; 18.
    - Narrative Progress Report. Economic Opportunity Program, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Status of Negroes in the Craft Unions…. Pittsburgh Labor market, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - The War on Poverty, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Office of The Mayor/The Mayor's advisory committee, 1974-1978; 19.
    - Citizen participation plan for the 1978 Urban Development Action Grant Application (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition Convention Center, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Departments, 1956-1979; 20.
    - Area Wage Survey: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, metropolitan area, U.S. Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Hazardous Material Spills and Responses for Municipalities, Final Report by Brinsko, George A., Hazardous Material Spill Research Branch, National Material Spill Research Center, c.1975 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - History and Status of the East Street Valley Expressway, Interstate Highway 279, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, U.S. General Accounting Office, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Metropolitan Pittsburgh Intrastate Air Quality Control Region, Air Pollution Report by Nagel, L. L., U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; Public Health Service, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Occupational Wage Survey, U.S. Department of Labor, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Occupational Wage Survey, U.S. Department of Labor, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Occupational Wage Survey, U.S. Department of Labor, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Statistical Profile; Pittsburgh, PA: Redevelopment Area, U.S. Bureau of the Census, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - The Model Cities Program, A Comparative Analysis of the Planning Process in Eleven Cities, U.S. Deptment of Housing and Urban Development, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - The Model Cities Program, Ten Model Cities; A Comparative Analysis of Second Round Planning Years, U.S. Deptment of Housing and Urban Development, c.1971 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Transportation Controls to Reduce Motor Vehicle Emissions In Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Tropical Storm Agnes Post Flood Report, Volume I Narrative Report, U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Pittsburgh District, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Tropical Storm Agnes Post Flood Report, Volume II Technical Report, U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Pittsburgh District, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Federation of Social Agencies: Bureau of Social Research, 1947; 21
    - Volume 1, Map Supplement, Recreational Facilities in Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Volume I, Recreational Facilities in Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Volume II, Recreational Facilities in Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Volume III, Recreational Facilities in Pittsburgh and Allegheny County (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1970-1974; 22
    - Membership Report as of September 30, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Reorganization Plan, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - A Report with options pertaining to school reorganization, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - The role of the Private Sector in Pittsburgh Public Schools by Schechter, Stephen, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh Board of Public Education, 1952-1979; 23
    - Annual Report of the Superintendent, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report of the Superintendent, Your Children are Learning, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report of the Superintendent, 100 Years in the Pittsburgh Public High Schoolds, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report of the Superintendent, Your Public Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report of the Superintendent, Here Are Your Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - The Annual Report of the Superintendent, 13 years of Progress in the Pittsburgh Public Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report of the Supertendent, The Pittsburgh Schools, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 1961 Annual Report of the Supertendent of Schools, Pupils, Patterns, and Possibilities (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, Superintendent of Schools and Secretary, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report for 1965, The Quest for Racial Equality in the Pittsburgh Public Schools (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Budget, Final 1971, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Budget Supplement, Preliminary 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1972, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1973, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1974, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1975, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Budget, Final 1975: 1975 Final General Fund Budget; 1975 Final Food Service Division Budget; 1974-75 Special Education Budget (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1976, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Budget, Final 1976: 1976 Final General Fund Budget; 1976 Final Food Service Division Budget, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Budget, Preliminary 1977, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Rules of The Board of Public Education of The School District Of Pittsburgh, Pennsylviania, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - School Improvement and Major Maintenance Program, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Department of Public Safety, 1947-1955; 24
    - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Department of Public Safety: Bureau of Fire, 1939-1983; 25
    - Annual Report, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Annual Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)